Hey, I'm Mike Toledo with Dentsime here in San Diego, California.
Now, I've had the opportunity to work with Jay since 2018, and I've always respected
the way he and his team at Superior PDR continue to push themselves to be the best.
That shows in their training, their work, and especially their approach of glupoing.
They care about the craft, they care about doing things the right way, and that matters
in this industry.
Now, I don't put my name behind just anything, but I am proud to endorse Jay and Superior
PDR.
If you're serious about learning glupoing, PDR training, and improving your skills, Superior
PDR is worth paying attention to.
My name is Mike Toledo.
Thanks for watching.